<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on AWS Modernization Workshop Sample</title>
    <link>/03_development.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on AWS Modernization Workshop Sample</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/03_development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stage Raw Data</title>
      <link>/03_development/01_stage_raw.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/03_development/01_stage_raw.html</guid>
      <description>Stage Raw Data In this video, we will demostrate how to install a package and then use the package to stage our data that lives in the S3 bucket.

Summary of this video: 1. Check a new branch. To do this, you will need to check out the main/master branch first and then click on create a new branch (feature/stage_tpch_data). If you get the button Pull from Remote, feel free to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transform Raw Data</title>
      <link>/03_development/02_modeling_data.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/03_development/02_modeling_data.html</guid>
      <description>Transform Raw Data In this video, we will be modeling our raw data into two staging models and one fact model, using dimensional modeling paradigms. We will be joining the two staging models (which have a 1:1 to the raw data source table) via the order_key as the foreign key.
For more information on how we structure our dbt project, click on this link. It should be noted that dbt is agnostic to all modeling paradigms (Data Vault, Kimball, etc).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Validate Code</title>
      <link>/03_development/03_use_ci_cd_workflow.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/03_development/03_use_ci_cd_workflow.html</guid>
      <description>Use CI/CD Workflow for Code Validation In this video, we will walk through - creating a good pull request - using a SlimCI job to validate your code - merging code into your production git branch - deploying the code to Redshift

Summary of this video:
 Commit any code that you might not have since the previous video. Click on Open Pull Request Fill out the Pull Request Template to the best of your abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
