<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS Dev Day Workshop with dbt on AWS Modernization Workshop Sample</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS Dev Day Workshop with dbt on AWS Modernization Workshop Sample</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Next Steps</title>
      <link>/05_closing/01_next_steps.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/05_closing/01_next_steps.html</guid>
      <description>
Thank you for joining us for this AWS Dev Day Workshop with dbt. We hope you learned a lot!
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in learning more about dbt, we recommend these resources:
 dbt Fundamentals course Join 15,000+ data professionals in our Slack community Contact our Team for more information about dbt at your org Join us at our Coalesce Conference  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup dbt Cloud Project</title>
      <link>/02_creating_the_workflow/01_create_dbt_project.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/02_creating_the_workflow/01_create_dbt_project.html</guid>
      <description>Setup dbt Cloud Project In this video, we will go through - setting up your dbt project - running and testing the sample models - see what it will look like to correct a broken test.

Summary of this video: 1. Click on the hamburger menu and click on Develop to go to the IDE. 2. To initialize the dbt project, click on the initialize your project. 3. Take a look around the project after it is initialized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stage Raw Data</title>
      <link>/03_development/01_stage_raw.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/03_development/01_stage_raw.html</guid>
      <description>Stage Raw Data In this video, we will demostrate how to install a package and then use the package to stage our data that lives in the S3 bucket.

Summary of this video: 1. Check a new branch. To do this, you will need to check out the main/master branch first and then click on create a new branch (feature/stage_tpch_data). If you get the button Pull from Remote, feel free to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tools</title>
      <link>/01_getting_started/01_the_tools.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01_getting_started/01_the_tools.html</guid>
      <description>The Tools In these videos, we will be providing a high level overview of the tools that we will be using for this workshop. We will be using Redshift, S3 Bucket, Github, and of course dbt. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about what other data warehouses/data lakes dbt supports, check out this link. dbt Cloud also works with all git providers with advanced functionality with Github and Gitlab.
In terms of understanding git for this workshop, dbt Cloud will guide you through a simplifed git workflow, where you don&amp;rsquo;t need to write a single git command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the Task</title>
      <link>/01_getting_started/02_overview_of_the_task.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01_getting_started/02_overview_of_the_task.html</guid>
      <description>Overview of the Task In this video, we will reviewing the four stages of our task:
 Setting up the workflow. Staging the raw data Transforming the raw data Use the CI/CD workflow to qualify the code before deployment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup CI/CD Workflow</title>
      <link>/02_creating_the_workflow/02_setup_cicd_flow.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/02_creating_the_workflow/02_setup_cicd_flow.html</guid>
      <description>Setup your Environments In this video, we will be creating the Production and CI/CD Environments that our jobs will run on.

Summary of this video: 1. To create the Production environment, click on Environments under the hamburger menu. Click on New Environment. Name the Environment. Keep the Deployment type and the default dbt version (which is always the latest stable version). Use your user&amp;rsquo;s Redshift credentials for the Deployment environment and called the schema analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transform Raw Data</title>
      <link>/03_development/02_modeling_data.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/03_development/02_modeling_data.html</guid>
      <description>Transform Raw Data In this video, we will be modeling our raw data into two staging models and one fact model, using dimensional modeling paradigms. We will be joining the two staging models (which have a 1:1 to the raw data source table) via the order_key as the foreign key.
For more information on how we structure our dbt project, click on this link. It should be noted that dbt is agnostic to all modeling paradigms (Data Vault, Kimball, etc).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup dbt Cloud and Github Repository</title>
      <link>/01_getting_started/03_sign_up_dbt_cloud_setup_repo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01_getting_started/03_sign_up_dbt_cloud_setup_repo.html</guid>
      <description>Sign up for dbt Cloud and Create a Github Repository In this video, we will to guide you through signing up for a trial dbt Cloud project and setting up a empty github repository. When creating your repository, be sure to not check off any of the files. You want a empty repository to connect to dbt cloud.

Helpful Tips  To sign up for a free dbt cloud account, you can go to this link and fill out the form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Validate Code</title>
      <link>/03_development/03_use_ci_cd_workflow.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/03_development/03_use_ci_cd_workflow.html</guid>
      <description>Use CI/CD Workflow for Code Validation In this video, we will walk through - creating a good pull request - using a SlimCI job to validate your code - merging code into your production git branch - deploying the code to Redshift

Summary of this video:
 Commit any code that you might not have since the previous video. Click on Open Pull Request Fill out the Pull Request Template to the best of your abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Redshift</title>
      <link>/01_getting_started/04_setup_redshift.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01_getting_started/04_setup_redshift.html</guid>
      <description>Setup Redshift and S3 To setup Redshift and S3, follow these steps:
 Log into AWS.
 Launch the stack. 
 Click Next till the end and then select acknowledgement checkbox. Then click &amp;ldquo;Create Stack&amp;rdquo;
 When the stack creation is complete, click on the Outputs tab to view information that you will use during rest of the workshop. Keep it handy.
  Setup External Schema In this video, we are going to walk you through creating an external schema in your Redshift Cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup dbt Cloud Account</title>
      <link>/01_getting_started/05_setup_dbt_cloud.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01_getting_started/05_setup_dbt_cloud.html</guid>
      <description>Setting up dbt Cloud account In this video, we will walk you through setting up your dbt Cloud account and dbt cloud project.

Summary of this video:
 The IDE is where we will be developing our dbt code. To setup the Redshift connection, you will need to choose Redshift as the data warehouse/database. Fill out the Redshift information from Cloudformation output. Your hostname is the entire hostname. The port is 5439 and the database is dbtworkshop.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
