<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on AWS Modernization Workshop Sample</title>
    <link>/01_getting_started.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on AWS Modernization Workshop Sample</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/01_getting_started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Tools</title>
      <link>/01_getting_started/01_the_tools.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01_getting_started/01_the_tools.html</guid>
      <description>The Tools In these videos, we will be providing a high level overview of the tools that we will be using for this workshop. We will be using Redshift, S3 Bucket, Github, and of course dbt. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about what other data warehouses/data lakes dbt supports, check out this link. dbt Cloud also works with all git providers with advanced functionality with Github and Gitlab.
In terms of understanding git for this workshop, dbt Cloud will guide you through a simplifed git workflow, where you don&amp;rsquo;t need to write a single git command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the Task</title>
      <link>/01_getting_started/02_overview_of_the_task.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01_getting_started/02_overview_of_the_task.html</guid>
      <description>Overview of the Task In this video, we will reviewing the four stages of our task:
 Setting up the workflow. Staging the raw data Transforming the raw data Use the CI/CD workflow to qualify the code before deployment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup dbt Cloud and Github Repository</title>
      <link>/01_getting_started/03_sign_up_dbt_cloud_setup_repo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01_getting_started/03_sign_up_dbt_cloud_setup_repo.html</guid>
      <description>Sign up for dbt Cloud and Create a Github Repository In this video, we will to guide you through signing up for a trial dbt Cloud project and setting up a empty github repository. When creating your repository, be sure to not check off any of the files. You want a empty repository to connect to dbt cloud.

Helpful Tips  To sign up for a free dbt cloud account, you can go to this link and fill out the form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Redshift</title>
      <link>/01_getting_started/04_setup_redshift.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01_getting_started/04_setup_redshift.html</guid>
      <description>Setup Redshift and S3 To setup Redshift and S3, follow these steps:
 Log into AWS.
 Launch the stack. 
 Click Next till the end and then select acknowledgement checkbox. Then click &amp;ldquo;Create Stack&amp;rdquo;
 When the stack creation is complete, click on the Outputs tab to view information that you will use during rest of the workshop. Keep it handy.
  Setup External Schema In this video, we are going to walk you through creating an external schema in your Redshift Cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup dbt Cloud Account</title>
      <link>/01_getting_started/05_setup_dbt_cloud.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01_getting_started/05_setup_dbt_cloud.html</guid>
      <description>Setting up dbt Cloud account In this video, we will walk you through setting up your dbt Cloud account and dbt cloud project.

Summary of this video:
 The IDE is where we will be developing our dbt code. To setup the Redshift connection, you will need to choose Redshift as the data warehouse/database. Fill out the Redshift information from Cloudformation output. Your hostname is the entire hostname. The port is 5439 and the database is dbtworkshop.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
